const data = [
    {
        "question": "Which state was the first colony established by the British?",
        "options": [
            "NSW",
            "Victoria",
            "Queensland",
            "Western Australia"
        ],
        "correct_option": "NSW",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the 'gold rush' start in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "1788",
            "1851",
            "1901",
            "1967"
        ],
        "correct_option": "1851",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Queensland's capital city?",
        "options": [
            "Sydney",
            "Melbourne",
            "Brisbane",
            "Perth"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Brisbane",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Commonwealth Coat of Arms represent?",
        "options": [
            "States and territories",
            "Australia's unity",
            "European settlement",
            "Gold rush"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Australia's unity",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which tree is Australia's national flower?",
        "options": [
            "Eucalyptus",
            "Wattle",
            "Jacaranda",
            "Acacia"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Wattle",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Australia's national anthem?",
        "options": [
            "Waltzing Matilda",
            "God Save the Queen",
            "Advance Australia Fair",
            "Southern Cross Anthem"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Advance Australia Fair",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Australia's capital city?",
        "options": [
            "Sydney",
            "Melbourne",
            "Brisbane",
            "Canberra"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Canberra",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which day celebrates the arrival of the First Fleet in 1788?",
        "options": [
            "Australia Day",
            "Anzac Day",
            "Remembrance Day",
            "Independence Day"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Australia Day",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of a Welcome to Country?",
        "options": [
            "Marks the start of an event",
            "Welcomes visitors to Aboriginal or Torres Strait Islander land",
            "Celebrates Australia Day",
            "Honors European settlement"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Welcomes visitors to Aboriginal or Torres Strait Islander land",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who were Australia's first inhabitants?",
        "options": [
            "British settlers",
            "Convicts",
            "Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples",
            "European explorers"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Governor of the colony of New South Wales?",
        "options": [
            "Captain James Cook",
            "Captain Arthur Phillip",
            "Governor Macquarie",
            "Prime Minister Robert Menzies"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Captain Arthur Phillip",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "When were the separate colonies united into the Commonwealth of Australia?",
        "options": [
            "1851",
            "1901",
            "1967",
            "2000"
        ],
        "correct_option": "1901",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the date of Australia Day?",
        "options": [
            "25 April",
            "26 January",
            "1 January",
            "15 August"
        ],
        "correct_option": "26 January",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which colors are present in the Australian National Flag?",
        "options": [
            "Red, white, and blue",
            "Green, black, and white",
            "Blue, white, and red",
            "Black, red, and yellow"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Blue, white, and red",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Southern Cross represent on the Australian National Flag?",
        "options": [
            "States and territories",
            "European settlement",
            "Native animals",
            "Group of stars in the southern sky"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Group of stars in the southern sky",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the green stripes represent on the Torres Strait Islander Flag?",
        "options": [
            "Torres Strait Islanders",
            "Land",
            "Sea",
            "Peace"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Land",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital city of Tasmania?",
        "options": [
            "Hobart",
            "Sydney",
            "Melbourne",
            "Brisbane"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Hobart",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which day is commemorated on 25 April each year?",
        "options": [
            "Australia Day",
            "Anzac Day",
            "Remembrance Day",
            "Independence Day"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Anzac Day",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Australia's national anthem?",
        "options": [
            "Waltzing Matilda",
            "God Save the Queen",
            "Advance Australia Fair",
            "Southern Cross Anthem"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Advance Australia Fair",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital city of Australia?",
        "options": [
            "Sydney",
            "Melbourne",
            "Brisbane",
            "Canberra"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Canberra",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Commonwealth Coat of Arms?",
        "options": [
            "The national anthem",
            "Australia’s national flower",
            "The official symbol of Australia, which identifies Commonwealth property",
            "The document that outlines the basic rules for the government"
        ],
        "correct_option": "The official symbol of Australia, which identifies Commonwealth property",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are Australia’s first inhabitants?",
        "options": [
            "British settlers",
            "Convicts",
            "Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples",
            "European explorers"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many states and territories are there in Australia?",
        "options": [
            "6 states, 2 territories",
            "7 states, 3 territories",
            "8 states, 2 territories",
            "6 states, 3 territories"
        ],
        "correct_option": "6 states, 2 territories",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the colors of the Australian Aboriginal Flag and what do they symbolize?",
        "options": [
            "Black, red, and yellow; representing the land, people, and sun",
            "Blue, white, and green; symbolizing the sea, sky, and land",
            "Red, white, and black; representing courage, peace, and unity",
            "Green, yellow, and red; symbolizing nature, sun, and fire"
        ],
        "correct_option": "Black, red, and yellow; representing the land, people, and sun",
        "topic": "australia_its_people"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many white stars are there on the Southern Cross constellation depicted on the Australian National Flag?",
        "options": [
            "4 stars",
            "5 stars",
            "6 stars",
            "7 stars"
        ],
        "correct_option": "5 stars"
    }
]

export default data;